shopyourworld.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

Overview 

Our customer’s privacy and security is of utmost importance to us. No really, it is. It’s more important than safeguarding the security pin number on our debit card. That is why we don’t sell or even ‘rent’ out personal information of our customers to third party organizations for their marketing strategies. In an event where your details are shared with an organization, it will be only after we’ve obtained your explicit consent and approval.   
Now that we’ve managed to put you at ease, a little bit at least, we request you to read our privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. We use your information only as described in our Privacy Policy. 

The privacy practices mentioned in this statement apply to all our services available under the domain and sub domains of www.shopyourworld.com (the ‘Site’) which is controlled and owned by Shop Your World Pte. Ltd (hereinafter referred to as ‘ShopYourWorld’ and/or ShopYourWorld.com) and apply generally to our affiliates, subsidiaries or joint venture websites. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please, do not use or access our Site. 

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you, as a part of the normal operation of our services, and what may happen to that information once submitted to us. Although this privacy policy document may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy,outlining all possible specifics, because we believe you should know as much as possible about ShopYourWorld's practices so that you can make informed decisions. Our subsidiaries and joint ventures operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy and, subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the global ShopYourWorld shopping community. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement at the time of registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the terms of the User Agreement. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on 15th April 2014  for all users. 

## 1\. Your Privacy - Our Commitment

At ShopYourWorld, we value your trust in us and are extremely proud of our commitment to protect your privacy. We strive to work hard to earn your confidence and loyalty so that you can actively use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site. 

## 2\. SHOP YOUR WORLD Privacy Guarantee

ShopYourWorld promises that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. From time to time we may reveal general statistical information (non-personally identifiable information) about our Website and visitors. This information may include number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc. We may also use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate, so that we can improve the Site and for business analysis and administrative purposes. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. 

## 3\. Information we collect

When you use our Site, we collect and store your personal information from you. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized shopping experience. This information allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Site to make your experience safer and easier.   
Importantly, we only collect that personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose and fulfilling your purchase orders, strictly on need-to-know basis. In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Using various data collection technology, our Site may track the amount of time spent on our website, categories of products browsed, search patterns etc, to give you an enhanced shopping experience.   
To fully use our Site, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you may be required to provide us with your contact and identity information, residence/place of business information, billing information, shipping information, bank account details and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Site.   
When provided with a ShopYourWorld ID by you, we may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.  
We use data collection devices such as ‘cookies’ on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. ‘Cookies’ are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a ‘cookie’. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are ‘session cookies,’ meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. Additionally, you may encounter ‘cookies’ or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a ‘cookie’ placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.  
If you choose to buy or make a purchase on the Site, we collect information about your buying behaviour. We also collect users' comments in our feedback area. If you establish a credit account with us to pay the fees we charge, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date.  
If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms, other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information as provided by you. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.  
If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.  
If you register for the Site on another web site or use a website providing a service for ShopYourWorld or a website that helps facilitates your activity on the Site, that web site is permitted to provide personal information about you to us.  

## 4\. Out use of your information

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe buying; measure consumer interest in the services provided by us, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services and updates, customize your experience, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our User Agreement and Terms and Conditions, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.  
By consenting to our Privacy Policy, you agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.  
You also agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, customer service and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information and communication. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time.  
We use personally identifiable information provided by you in order to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site. We also track your past purchases to provide you with a personalized profile of your shopping history. In addition, we may notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information.  

## 5\. Our disclosure of your information/ When and how we share your information

We may also use your information to deliver communication to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as new services and promotions. The following are examples of some categories of persons to whom we would share your information with from time-to-time. 

## 1\. Advertisements

  * a. 

Where a user enters information on any form of an advertiser, the information is simultaneously collected by ShopYourWorld and the advertiser. The information is used by ShopYourWorld in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and is used by the advertiser as per the advertiser’s prevalent privacy policies. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these advertisers, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to provide the said information. 

  * b. 

ShopYourWorld may also aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. 

## 2\. Classifieds Listings

  * a. 

When a user lists a classified advertisement, and the advertisement receives an expression of interest by the interested user, the interested user will be provided the contact information of the user listing the advertisement as provided in that user's registration forms. 

  * b. 

When a user expresses an interest in a classified advertisement, the user who has listed the advertisement will be provided the contact information of the interested user as provided in the interested user's registration form. 

## 3\. Items and Services offered on the Site by third parties

There are certain items and services for which third parties request for information before the item/service is listed on the Site. The information provided by the user for such purposes is simultaneously collected by ShopYourWorld and the respective third party. This information is utilised by the third party in accordance with their privacy policy and the terms of the offer. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services. 

## 4\. Internal Service Providers

We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on the Site (e.g., search technology, discussion boards, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, co-branded credit cards) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced Site related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as for Site surveys or for a co-branded credit card). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy. 

## 5\. Other Corporate Entities

We share much of our data, including personal information about you, with our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures that are committed to serving your online buying needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. ShopYourWorld, its affiliates, subsidiaries, its joint ventures, or any combination of such, will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we plan to, merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding, involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

## 6\. Legal Requests

We cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the community from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, UserID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena.   
Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, pin/zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name to Intellectual Property Right's owners under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.  
Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.  

## 6\. What about children's privacy?

Children are not eligible to use our Site and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you cannot sell or purchase any items on the Site. If you wish to purchase or sell an item on the Site, such purchase or sale may be made by your legal guardian or parents who have registered as users of the Site provided that such purchase or sale is not in relation to any adult material/mature audience items displayed on the Site, the sale or purchase of which to/by minors is strictly prohibited. 

## 7\. Access or change your personally identifiable information

To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally-identifying information. If you have registered your profile on ShopYourWorld, your ShopYourWorld ID and Password are required in order to access your profile information. 

## 8\. Security

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. 

## 9\. Your Consent

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site by ShopYourWorld. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our Website at least 10 days in advance of implementation. 

## 10\. Tell us what you think

At SHOP YOUR WORLD, we welcome your questions and comments regarding our privacy policy. You may contact SHOP YOUR WORLD at [legal@shopyourworld.com](mailto:legal@shopyourworld.com).
